<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">eBayFriend</string>
    <string name="title_activity_buy">BuyActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="buy_it_now">Buy</string>
    <string name="buy_name">Dior</string>
    <string name="buy_price">$2250.00</string>
    <string name="buy_discription">&#x0009;The trail of its invention leads back to precisely 1695, and supposedly to Giovanni Paolo Feminis, an Italian living in Cologne, Germany, who gave this new olfactive composition the name of his adopted city. Ever since its creation, Eau de Cologne has been a citrus scent, admired for its fresh and light notes of rosemary, lemon balm, bergamot, neroli, citron and lemon. But beyond its olfactory refinement, it was its medicinal virtues that, at the time, found the most favor. Bracing, reinvigorating and curative, eau de Cologne – having quickly become an essential of daily life - was thus prescribed by doctors. In the 19th century, it cemented its place as a grand classic of perfumery. Throughout the following century, Eau de Cologne would inspire perfumers, with each coming up with their very own version. Christian Dior was one of these and in 1953, with the perfumer Edmond Roudnitska, created the very first unisex scent in the history of perfumery. It was a Cologne, and given the name  Eau Fraîche. Worn by Christian Dior himself, the light and dynamic fragrance was dreamt up in harmony with the fashion of the time: chiffons, cotton fabrics, chic sportswear styles.</string>
    <string name="newsfeed_play">71‘’   ❤</string>
    <string name="pull_to_refresh_pull_label">Pull to refresh&#8230;</string>
    <string name="pull_to_refresh_release_label">Release to refresh&#8230;</string>
    <string name="pull_to_refresh_refreshing_label">Loading&#8230;</string>
    <string name="pull_to_refresh_tap_label">Tap to refresh&#8230;</string>
    <string name="no_more_label">No more items to be loaded&#8230;</string>
    <string name="selectItem">please select the item </string>
    <string name="mainview_post">post</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chat">ChatActivity</string>
    <string name="record">Record</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="post">Post</string>
    <string name="style1">Emboss</string>
    <string name="style2">Paint</string>
    <string name="style3">Black</string>
    <string name="style4">Original</string>
    <string name="next">Next  →</string>

</resources>